<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Sent to the partner (Loan Owner) the loan is in underwriting review</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Loan Submitted - Awaiting Review Notification to Partner</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Loan Submitted - {!Loan_New__c.LoanNumber__c}, {!Loan_New__c.Client_Name__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>ORMS Support

ormservices.com

Hello {!Contact.FirstName},

Thank you for your business!  Your loan has been submitted to my team and we will begin reviewing the submission package shortly.
After the file review is complete, we will begin ordering services (FHA Case Number, Appraisal and Title/Escrow). *State cooling off periods may apply (CA)

Title Order Process
ORMS will order title/open escrow as you requested from: {!Loan_New__c.Title_Company__c} {!Loan_New__c.Contact_Name__c} {!Loan_New__c.Contact_Phone_Number_LoanDetails__c} {!Loan_New__c.Contact_Email__c}

Appraisal Order Process
ORMS will order the appraisal through MIS (Mortgage Information Services).
MIS will locate an appraiser within 24 hours and once an appraiser has been assigned, MIS will email {!Loan_New__c.Preferred_Contact_Name__c} for the appraisal payment.
Once you make the payment through the link provided, the appraiser will contact the borrower to schedule the inspection.  If {!Loan_New__c.Related_Partner__c} is covering the cost of the appraisal, please save and upload the receipt to Portal so we can get you reimbursed on the HUD-1 settlement.
Note: CA properties require a carbon monoxide detector and double strapped water heater.  Please ensure your borrower have these set up and installed prior to the appraisal inspection.  This will save your borrower both time and money ($150 re-inspection fee or 1004-D).


PCS/Underwriting
Once your file has been underwritten (24-48 hours), you will receive conditions via email direction from {!Loan_New__c.PCS_at_Partner_Level__c}, your Partner Care Specialist.
{!Loan_New__c.PCS_at_Partner_Level__c}  will be your main point of contact now that the file has been submitted and will help you get this to closing.  Contact information is as below:
{!Loan_New__c.PCS_at_Partner_Level__c}, ORMS Partner Care Specialist
Direct:   {!Loan_New__c.PCS_Phone__c}
{!Loan_New__c.PCS_Email__c}


Let me know if you have any questions.

Thank you.

4445 Eastgate Mall, Ste 320, San Diego, CA 92121</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
