<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>ORMS Wholesale Pricing Non Helo</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>One Reverse Mortgage - Pricing 9-18-2018</subject>
    <textOnly>ORMS Pricing
September 18, 2018

Hi {!Contact.FirstName}

Attached is our most current pricing sheet.

Does it seem like your clients are confused about the reverse mortgage line of credit? The line of credit may seem complicated, but it’s easy for clients to use. Here’s how we describe the HECM Line of Credit:

- “How does the reverse mortgage line of credit grow?” Unused funds in the line of credit will grow over time in accordance with your growth rate. This value is determined from several values including: 1) the current index value 2) the margin and 3) the annual mortgage insurance premium that is paid to the FHA. As an adjustable rate, your growth rate may vary over time.
- “What if I change my mind and want a lump sum?” You can use the funds in your line of credit however you wish; if you choose, you could withdraw all of the money at once as a lump sum or elect to receive monthly disbursements. Otherwise, these funds will remain available for use in your line of credit as they grow.
- “Can I get a fixed rate reverse mortgage line of credit?” At the moment, the reverse mortgage line of credit is only available as an adjustable rate loan.

You can now run clients who are 62+ through our scenario calculator to see what they could qualify for. If you do not have access to the portal yet, please attend a training session by clicking on a link below.

Please reach out if you have any questions. I am here to help!

CURRENT TURN TIMES
New Registration  30 minutes * May increase based on volume levels
Submit to UW for Conditional Approval  24 hours
Conditions Review  24 hours
Clear to Close  24 hours
Docs to Closing Agent  24 hours * From Final HUD Approval


ON DEMAND REVERSE
MORTGAGE TRAINING

PORTAL TOUR

Self-paced webinar designed to get you familiar with our site where you can run scenarios to see if a client qualifies for a reverse mortgage, access marketing collateral, and more in-depth training.

REVERSE MORTGAGE 101

Self-paced webinar designed to get you familiar with reverse mortgage eligibility requirements and all the basics you need to begin originating loans today.

Thank you for your business!

Best,
{!Contact.OwnerFullName}
{!Contact.OwnerEmail}
{!Contact.OwnerTitle}
{!Contact.OwnerPhone}

Follow us on Facebook &amp; Twitter!</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
